drsays.com 2013-08-05

# Privacy Policy | DrSays

Last modified: March 2, 2011

DRSAYS LLC values the privacy rights of its website users. This Privacy Policy for the DRSAYS website, (“Site”) operated by DRSAYS LLC,  describes the information that is collected from you as part of the normal operation of this Site, and how we use and disclose this information.

By using this Site and DRSAYS services, you expressly consent to our collection, use and disclosure of personal information as laid out in this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of the services and site following the posting of any changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to our Terms of Use. 

In this Privacy Policy, we use the following terms to describe different types of Users on our Site: our customers who use the DRSAYS portal to provide health services are called “Health Professionals”, our customers who elect to create a profile are called DRSAYS "Members". These people are collectively described in this Privacy Policy as “Users” of our Site.

**1\. Information Collected.  **Visitors are welcome to browse our site anonymously, but Users wishing to use Site services are asked to provide: 1) various contact and identity information; 2) billing information; 3) medical information; 4) other personal information as indicated (forms indicate what info is required, and what info is optional). 

**2\. Personal Non-medical Information.  **Any personal non-medical information obtained from your current and past activities on the Site is used to: 1) provide to you the services offered by the Site; 2) bill for services rendered; 3) troubleshoot problems; 4) detect any error, fraud and other criminal activity; 5) enforce the Terms of Use; 6) provide system or administrative messages, and as otherwise described at the time of collection; 7) get feedback on services; 8) analyze site usage; 9) improve content and product offerings; 10) customize the Site’s content layout and services.

**3\. Billing and Payment Information.  **We use credit card and other payment information you submit to us on the Site only to process payments you make through the Site. Credit card information and other sensitive personal information required to process a credit decision is not used for any other purpose by us or our financial services providers (like Authorize.Net or PayPal), and will not be kept longer than necessary for providing the services.

**4\. Use of Cookies.  **DRSAYS collects anonymous information about visitors to our website in the form of cookies for site statistics purposes only. Cookies are pieces of information transferred to the browsing computer and used for record-keeping purposes. Cookies generally assist users by performing certain functions such as saving passwords and personal preferences regarding the sites.  Use of cookies is not linked to any personally identifiable information while visiting the DRSAYS site. Information collected includes IP address, referring website, duration of stay, time/date, etc.  Once users close their browser, cookies simply terminate. Except as described in this Policy, we do not use information transferred through cookies for any promotional or marketing purposes. We will not sell, share or lease this information to others. DRSAYS does not sell any customer lists or e-mail addresses cookies or other data.

**5\. Medical Information.  **Only Health Professionals and DRSAYS staff members will have access to personal health information (PHI). DRSAYS will only release PHI to comply with legal requirements as set forth by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), as discussed below, and other applicable state and federal laws. Upon disclosure of PHI, we will attempt to contact the patient as permitted by regulations or judgments by a court of law to notify of the release of patient information.

According to HIPAA, you have the right to:

• View your medical records. HIPAA guarantees you can access your medical records within 30 days. 

• Receive a notice that tells you how your health information may be used and shared.

• For certain purposes, you always have the decision whether or not to give permission for your health information to be shared before it’s used or shared. Your chosen Health Professionals using DRSAYS do not use or share your personally identifiable medical records for any other purposes that aren’t part of normal, routine health care processes.

• Get a report on when and why your health information was shared for specific legal purposes.

**6\. Links.  **Our Web Sites may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that DRSAYS is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites, and this Web Site Privacy Statement does not apply to such sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

**7\. Disclosure of Information.  **DRSAYS will never sell or rent your information to third parties. But here are some of the ways your information may be disclosed:

7.1 Members and Customers, Etc.

In the normal operation of the Site your medical information is disclosed to the Health Professionals you choose, and you can see information about Health Professionals, such as address, fees, a list of colleagues, as a Member. In general, the information you enter on the site is only available to the people you decide to share it with.

7.2 Legal Requests and Emergencies

We cooperate with law enforcement inquiries and demands for information that are made under force of law. If it’s what we believe is an emergency situation, we may provide personal information to law enforcement agencies. We may also provide personal information where required by statute, court order, legal process or lawful authority. Lastly, we may provide it to our legal counsel in connection with the foregoing.

**8\. Data Access and Security.  **DRSAYS has developed all systems and manages the data for this site. No data is transferred to users that do not have specific data access keys. Personal information collected by our web site is stored in secure operation environments that are not available to the public. We take every reasonable precaution to protect your personal information including encryption and passwords when appropriate. Only those staff members of DRSAYS with relevant business duties (for example, a customer service representative) may access personal information on the site to perform those specific duties, each having signed confidentiality agreements. Any staff member who violates our privacy or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution. 

DRSAYS welcomes your questions and comments about privacy and this policy. If you have any questions about our policies or our site, please Contact Us.
